10 years in prison and fine
Punishment of 70 billion won
About JS Group Chairman Jang Hyun-bae
exceeding everyone's expectations
While sentencing a heavy sentence
He suddenly emerged as a national judge.
An elementary school classmate
You called
- Kim Joo-seop?
- oh my!
People's judge!
Go for it!
In the car of the judge of the corruption unit
It’s a box of apples worth 1.2 billion won…
After graduating from high school
Almost like an orphan
A bastard like you who has no roots
Me, who believed in me and pulled me in
Are you betraying me like this?
You viper-like bastard!
this human
who was tried by me before
He's a habitual fraudster named Yoo Jae-beom.
Currently wanted!
Submit your resignation immediately.
Come to our firm
Because I convinced my dad
You convinced Dr. Oh Gyu-jang?
I think you should help me out.
I am those bonobonos
Welcome!
I'll take care of it for just one year.
Do you want to make a deal?
The incident that made me quit being a judge
You never asked?
Have you seen the video?
It's been a while
CEO Jaebeom Yoo
Yes, it's been a while.
CEO Oh
Don't be fooled by David Kang
He is a huge bribe taker.
a good businessman
driven to death
- He is a brutal murderer.
- Park Byun?
No matter how you look at it, it's Attorney Kang.
There are no signs of manipulation
Is this the judge's room phone number?
What are you talking about!
I never once
I got on the phone with that person...
good morning!
Yoon Ina is a working-level officer.
people you meet
You asked me to identify you.
- Uh
- Where Judge Kang worked
Chief Justice of Seoul Central District Court
- what?
- As a new Supreme Court Justice
Seoul Central District Court Chief Justice Shin Jung-seok
Appointed to the President
Created by secretary Seo who quit
This is a transcript.
my father
Regarding the appeal case of Chairman Jang Hyun-bae
It was about a phone call.
What division of the Supreme Court?
My appearance under anesthesia
Are you saying it was like this?
Yeah
Retrospective amnesia effect
'I'm not drunk'
‘I was asleep’?
my case
I heard you would take care of it
The judge in charge abused his power
With a rigged trial
made my father die
The name of the judge in charge...
This is Kang David
“O&Partners”
Let's go out and talk for a moment.
That's right
one trial
Are you making a fuss?
I take that as a compliment, doctor.
I went all the way to the National Assembly and won.
Please reconsider disbanding the team.
Dismantled?
attracting clients
I fulfilled the wagering conditions well.
What does that mean?
ah…
our client
It's not Elijah, it's EK Entertainment...
EK Enter
The representative is arrested
All of my assets have been provisionally confiscated, so I am an empty shell.
I can't believe it
You want penniless clients?
A child named Elijah
Now you yourself
Are you planning to set up an agency?
Of course, with our O&Partners
Any legal advice agreement
I'm going to sign it
Right? Kang Lawyer
Well done
Wow…
It's called O&Partners.
I was nervous, but this…
The office is also unique and nice.
Lawyer
It's you, right?
What do you mean?
uh
I am disappointed, Attorney Gippeum Park.
No, helping the powerless
Aren’t you a public interest lawyer?
But even after receiving this public interest tip,
Have you been crushing it all this time?
Hey, after all, lawyers are the same.
Actually
Are your arms bent inward or outward?
powerless people
Won, I’m sad…
I have nothing to say to scammers.
sleep anesthesia
Did you use drugs?
Hahahaha
Hey, this is an honor.
A giant in the legal profession
Hearing Dr. Oh’s praise
Ah, it's usually not that difficult.
that difficult task
I do it, hahahaha
It's probably not a giant tree, but a monster.
Who, who said that...
No, the legal profession has always
As a role model I respect Dr.
It's okay
I
I like monsters better
I mean they're scared, people
By the way
My only daughter
I raised him too much
A spoiled and naughty calf
Hasn’t it happened?
I'm a bit worried
Is that possible?
I always
You are a daughter who listens well to your father.
I only know my father
Benzodiazepine series
It must have been drugs
Using short-term memory loss
To a crazy person
Putting on a box of apples
Turn it over like it's a cash box
yes, that's right
fish oil
You’re amazing, Attorney Park?
Are you admitting it?
Yes, I admit it.
It's just as you said.
Well, there are some more details.
um
Then now
You need to ask about the motive for the crime.
- The motive for the crime?
- Yes
I am a candidate for Supreme Court Justice
Against national judge David Kang
Why did you have to do that?
On the subject of being on the run for fraud
Why on my own
Did you appear in front of the lawyer?
Shouldn’t you be asking that?
‘Attorney Kang was a judge’
'With a rigged trial
'I made my father die'
Why on earth is Attorney Kang
Would you do something like that?
Let’s ask that directly, that…
Hmm…
To Kang David
Ha, something
It seems like you have a deep story, but
Look at me now
Are you telling me to believe that?
with false images
What about someone who falsely accuses a co-worker?
no
not my words
Trust the evidence
It's all here
This is what I've collected over the past 10 years.
I'll read it though
I will believe you
Don't get your hopes up
And Attorney Kang
For framing someone with a false video
You will have to take responsibility
oh
Are you trying to report me?
yes, you should
No, you can't do it?
Why can't I do it...
just happened to me
You decided to review it, right?
'A lawyer learns something in the course of his or her job.
'You must not reveal secrets'
You have a duty of confidentiality, right?
Oh my
Even during the consultation process
Now~
Then
Please review it carefully.
Please come visit me
A visit?
yes
That
Isn’t he a habitual fraudster on the run?
I'm going to turn myself in to the police.
Lawyer
see
I risked everything
About me
I don't mind going to hell
David Kang, his hypocrisy
If you can reveal it
Ah, it's a bit surprising, isn't it?
I thought you were going to make a fuss?
Did you do something, Dad?
Huh?
under… There's definitely something there
be careful
My brother and the pro bono team
Well, what should I do...
Hey, why...
Oh, that's not right
It's not right, it's not right
Dr. Oh recently
Find out who you came into contact with.
both inside and outside
no
O&Partners visitor list
- Attorney Park
- Yes
What's going on?
That person earlier
It seemed familiar somehow.
No
Oh, that…
I was introduced to you by an external organization.
First, I will review the records.
I'll tell you
yes, i understand
If you have anything to discuss, let me know anytime.
Yes, thank you, Attorney Jang.
No
Lawyer Kang!
Why do you look like that?
Is it really going to be disbanded?
Our team?
huh?
No, Doctor Oh.
Aren’t you coming to meet me?
- I came to see you.
- Ha…
Filed a lawsuit against the client
I heard you just got angry.
We really just
Are you just going to sit on the street like this?
Why are you making such a fuss?
You did a case that a lawyer should have handled.
That's it then
Hey! you all morning
I just feel anxious
Same documents over and over again
I was reading it 100 times, really.
- Do you want to act cool, really?
- Well, when will I!
under! Yoo Nan-hee?
yes?
I received praise
Star clients like Elijah
I caught it
- Ugh!
- Wow, wow, what!
Ugh, what!
Ouch! Ouch!
Hey, you but
What did you just talk about?
Aren't you working? Taking the obvious...
Ah, Yoo Nan-hee
Look at the change in attitude, really.
Park Byeon-eun
Why do you look so unhappy?
Didn't you hear what I said?
Oh, our team isn’t disbanded?
yes
I love it so much
Oh, thank you for your hard work
Thank you for your hard work
Lawyer Kang
What Dr. Oh Gyu-jang once said
The one who takes it easily
You're not
You had a hard time
Hey, what's going on, Park Byun?
Yeah, no, what happened?
Come on! We feel good too
Let's go for an early lunch.
How about boiled pork in dogani stew at Grandma’s house?
- oh!
- Oh, great.
Hey, you like Park Byun Crucible.
yes, that's good
Ah!
This, this, this, this
A complete melting pot of joy?
Hahahahaha!
her…
Isn't it really bad?
I'm having fun?
Well, what's fun?
Isn't it fun?
under…
“Joie de viva”
What is it?
hmm…
No, 7:30
No, time…
wow…
No, what's going on?
Like this…
You want to have a meeting early?
Sister, public defense is also a worker.
A sweet morning sleep is a basic right
Could this be related to Attorney Kang?
uh?
What do you mean?
Only Attorney Kang is absent.
The person Attorney Park interviewed yesterday
Person introduced by the Justice Victims Solidarity
Right?
Victim of justice?
No way, when Attorney Kang was a judge,
Who was on trial?
That's right
Hey, what else can I say...
under!
Hey, then, what?
What, lawyer Kang, what, huh?
What, you mean it was a rigged trial?
uh
That's exactly what it sounds like
- Huh?
- uh?
Wait a minute
Cases sent by that organization
I've seen a few too.
Most of them are baseless speculations, right?
Yeah, if you think you lost unfairly
First of all, the judge is suspicious.
uh
Ha, by the way
I brought the basis
So, let's have a meeting.
Yoo Jae-beom’s father came to visit me.
Mr. Yoo Baek-man
It's called Woongcheon Paper.
Originally a paper manufacturing company in the Ungcheon area.
He was a businessman who ran
Moved to Jangwol Industrial Complex
Then, as the business expanded,
The factory was moved to Jangwol Industrial Complex in the metropolitan area.
Let's move
But 10 years ago
tragedy at the factory
A fire accident occurs
It's fire!
The factory burned down
There were also deaths
Ha, oh my...
Due to aging of electrical facilities
It was discovered that a short circuit was the cause.
There were also insufficient evacuation facilities.
The factory manager, who is in charge of on-site safety,
I was arrested and indicted
The judge in charge of that case was...
It was Judge Kang.
- Yes
- Ha…
Wait a minute
That, Jaebeom Yoo?
His father is the owner of the company?
not the factory manager
- Right.
- But why...
the defendant
I changed it, Attorney Kang.
Huh?
ex officio
bail the defendant
Judge
The trial is starting now.
What are you talking about?
Not the factory manager
the president of this company
Come catch Yoo Man-man.
Otherwise I can’t do it.
this trial
On the first trial, the judge
Factory manager ex officio
You said you made bail?
That's rare, right?
That's out loud
Are you showing your feelings?
Moreover, to the prosecutor
You even commanded the investigation.
Change the defendant to the president
Wow, Attorney Kang.
As expected, even when I was a judge, this…
- He wasn't an ordinary person.
- Junwoo.
That
I don't think it's something to admire, does it?
Can a judge cross the line?
Yes, anyway
Very lawyer-like work.
It started to happen
Huh?
If it's something that is worthy of Attorney Kang...
You called me
reporter
There's a fuss at the desk.
Do you have any sexy items?
During the last LNG explosion accident
It was too late then
How bad was it?
Oh no, don't say anything.
um
What is this?
Does this look like cup ramen?
Woongcheon Paper Factory
You know the fire incident, right?
yes?
Oh, that person died?
Did this come from that scene?
a dead friend
He was a trainee at a public engineering high school.
seventeen years old
Wow
This is from his backpack.
Eat one of these
I guess I was trying to work overtime
Oh my~
Oh, so?
Baby, please tell me in detail.
Judge Kang
Yeah, yeah
Ah
no
Let's not toast
Huh?
Now
I know that picture of cup ramen
That was all over the news.
Lawyer Kang
You spilled it.
Ha…
something so
What Attorney Kang would do
It's work, though.
From then on
Very magical things
It has begun
Protests take place
Media reports continue
Protesters say this tragedy
It wasn't just an accident...
The prosecution didn't budge
They really want to indict business owner Yoo Baek-man.
Detective!
Including the factory manager
Those involved changed their words one after another.
Statement unfavorable to Yu Baek-man
Start doing it
In the end
defendant
Yes, your honor.
Definitely once
There's something I wanted to ask
Yes?
Ah, yes, yes, yes
working at the defendant's factory
To workers too
The thought of having a loving family
Have you ever tried it?
yes?
Of course...
they
It is not a machine that only makes money.
A person made of blood and flesh
Do you know?
I…
Judge
I am
Me, the company…
I pronounce judgment
the defendant
Sentenced to 7 years in prison
I…
Judge!
The defendant is detained in court
- Okay, Judge! No
- Execute
Judge, Judge
Judge, my words.
Please just listen to me
Judge!
- It's unfair, Judge.
- Stay still!
- Hey, hey, wait a minute.
- Judge!
- Judge.
- Wait a minute...
and…
No, back then
State, serious disaster punishment law
Isn’t that a time when it wasn’t there?
7 years in prison
This is the highest sentence under the Occupational Safety and Health Act.
And individual business owners?
How did you get through the higher level review?
10 years ago
Right after the Sewol Ferry
Ah…
Oh, I guess so.
In full swing
about social disaster
There must have been a lot of criticism
He's a courageous young judge.
Articles are pouring in
I guess I got noticed, from then on.
Ha…
something so
Lawyer Kang is so
It's something to do
Why not?
- huh?
- fact
I hated Attorney Kang at first.
It was obvious
But as we continued to work together,
'Even people like this
'Can't there be at least one person?'
‘The thing called law’
‘I’m on the side of the strong anyway.’
‘At least once like this’
‘If I win’
‘If you give me at least some hope that I can win’
‘How good would it be?’
‘To those who always lose’
- Attorney Yoo
- Isn't that also the case with this case?
Lawyer Kang
Even though I’m a snob about the religion
Doing something that doesn't exist
I'm not the one to make it happen
Obviously the business owner
I must have done something bad that deserves responsibility.
Because it doesn't work like it is!
Lawyer Kang
Even by using all means
In the end, I would have made them responsible.
Isn't it? uh?
Doesn’t everyone think that way?
Nanhee
Mr. Yoo Baek-man died in prison.
- With a vase
- Yes?
uh?
Jaebeom Yoo received it
This is the factory manager’s autobiography.
‘At that time, Judge David Kang’
'Blatantly to Mr. Yoo Baek-man
Towards shifting responsibility’
‘The trial proceeded’
'He kept pace with it.
'I had no choice but to make a statement'
Did you really go that far?
operation…
It's a rigged trial...
If that's true
Oh, you're a criminal?
Lawyer Kang
Ha…
yes
no
But we
I can't handle this case.
Isn't it?
under…
Attorney Kang is our team leader.
You're a colleague!
Besides, the team leader
If something like this becomes a problem
Our team is already in a precarious situation.
It's flying, isn't it?
I barely won and survived.
Well, how did you win...
brother
Ha…
under…
Wow
baba baba
Good morning!
Oh, everyone came out early?
Ah~
Ah, why are you so down?
Oh, what's the problem?
say something
Hey, Jang Byeon!
Throw away the broken one and let’s go
Now let's write this
Oh, to Dr. Oh
If the team is praised
It should be like this
Isn't that right, Yu Byun?
You like coffee
The atmosphere is so cold
I'm going to go to the data room.
- Come on, let's go together.
- Uh...
The data room is here, but where...
Lawyer Kang
Huh?
Please talk to me for a moment.
What, what, what...
Jaebeom Yoo, that person came to visit?
- Yes
-Why, why didn’t you tell me…
Uh, uh, where are you? that human
Lawyer Kang
Why don't you call me
What did you do!
Not the time to be like this, ah…
Oh no
Uh, Detective Woo, here I am.
- Now that person, Jaebeom Yoo…
- under…
I surrendered, Jaebeom Yoo.
Uh, I'll do it again.
You did embroidery?
Yes, I'm in jail now.
Oh, then
Are you admitting that you framed me?
I'm sorry, but I can't tell you that.
Why, why? Why, why...
Why are you saying I can't speak?
They came looking for me
I anyway
As a lawyer, I heard the story.
Oh, well, no way, now, well
I decided to defend that person.
Park Byun?
Oh, are you out of your mind, Attorney Park?
No, I haven't decided yet.
Then why!
During the consultation process
Confidentiality obligations apply.
You know very well.
Ana, Jaebeom Yoo, that person is really…
No, at first it was to Park Byeon.
He sent me a video of an apple box.
This time you came to me to defend me?
Are you accusing me of nothing?
Such shameless Mr.
no
So, the fraud case that Ji was on the run from?
- Attorney Kang
- Then what is it!
You know me as Yoo Baek-man, right?
Who is that?
I don't know, I'm that kind of person
This is Jaebeom Yoo’s father.
CEO
The last week you mentioned
This is the list of visitors.
Oh, good job, team leader.
No, this person came here?
Who is he, sir?
Who were you visiting?
Team dedicated to public interest
I am a lawyer named Park Gi-ppeum.
Jaebeom Yoo is that human son?
Boy, how…
then…
Do you remember now?
Who is Yoo Baek-man?
Ah, yes
yes, i remembered
He's someone I used to judge.
It must be that person's son
I didn't even think about it
Jaebeom Yoo
Lawyer Kang
I believe it was a rigged trial.
Sounds that don't even sound like words...
Hey, I
Do you look like that kind of person?
A rigged trial? What are you looking at me for?
- No?
- Of course...
Of course not!
I just did what was legal.
Yeah, whatever.
Because of that resentment
Are you saying it was a trap?
Ha, sorry
I can't tell you that.
Ah…
Jaebeom Yoo
He said he collected it himself.
With rigged trial evidence
came to see me
Please sue Attorney Kang.
I'm doing it
To our pro bono team
What evidence did you bring?
I can't tell you, I'm sorry.
child, child, child
Ah, ah, ah!
ah!
So are you going to do it?
Against me?
First of all, Attorney Kang.
I want to listen to you first.
Me
I am a person without a single bit of shame.
I just did what I had to do
yes
So please tell me everything
What happened?
At that trial
yes, i will
But
There's someone I need to meet.
Ha…
This peppermint candy
This
This is
I founded this firm
This is what I ate every day when I stayed up all night.
At that time, the lawyer
There were only three of us
You said it, father.
Because that candy has been discontinued
By taking over the factory
You made me make it again
Was it like that?
Oh my, is dementia already here?
Let's be still
What time was it today?
Why did you do that?
What do you mean?
You know
Jaebeom Yoo
Well?
why
I don't know why you came and asked me?
under…
You played a very risky card.
father
This is in our firm itself
It will be a threat
well
Bring the transcript
The father was threatening
I don’t know what you want to say, Jeongin?
Created by secretary Seo who quit
This is a transcript.
my father
Regarding the appeal case of Chairman Jang Hyun-bae
It was about a phone call.
What division of the Supreme Court?
Um…
No matter how much I
When I turn around, it fades away
Even though he is an old man
You were hasty, Jeong In-ah.
Shouldn't you have waited a little longer?
I should have been a daughter who listened to my father well.
Abby is still useful.
yes
You put away your troubles
How about picking up a hobby?
huh?
I'll decline
I'm still busy
This perm made by my father
To protect me from my father
no
You will rest.
Today is the day
Isn’t it a perfect day?
As a gift...
What is that...
Oh, yes, that's right, that's right
2 o'clock today
2 o'clock
This is just news
By former judge David Kang
Sentenced to 10 years in prison
was arrested in court
The case of JS Group Chairman Jang Hyun-bae
Just from the Supreme Court
It was remanded on the grounds of not guilty.
- Chairman Jang Hyun-bae’s side
- Ha…
Meanwhile, former judge David Kang
Decide on a conclusion
They said it was an unreasonable piece of trial.
I've been criticizing
With this Supreme Court ruling
Chairman Jang’s argument
The weight has been put on
- Ha…
- the incident
-Remanded to the High Court
- Oh my...
While a new trial is scheduled for
- The High Court ruled against former Judge David Kang...
- Uh, bro, bro, what's wrong?
- Hey, are you okay?
- Oh, it's okay.
Supreme Court
How to reflect the judgment of innocence...
No, but what is it really?
How does this work?
Chairman Jang Hyun-bae's case
Are you saying this is a rigged trial?
No, that can't be possible.
sister
Where is Attorney Kang now?
uh? uh…
I said I was going to meet someone for a moment.
Ah, meeting means meeting someone.
In this mess!
under…
Ah, our national judge David Kang!
Hey David, it's been a while, me.
I'm Joo-jeop, huh?
Hahahaha…
Are you laughing?
thank you
Let's take care of it...
who is this?
Who are you planning this with?
With whom?
oh…
Are you curious about that?
You don’t ask ‘why’?
Actually
You know that now, right?
then my father
Did you also hear that he passed away?
Against the incumbent chief judge
Even after doing this
Did you think it would be okay?
Mmm, um, um
I am no longer a sitting judge.
you
The price for all these pranks
You will receive it in abundance.
Really?
How?
Catching you was the problem.
Revealing what you did
It wasn't even a thing
- Do you know?
- Oh, is that so?
If you know it, it’s not a big deal.
My drink was poisoned, right?
When I went to the bathroom
No?
my friend
I'll see what goes first.
- Okay, here we go.
- Okay, uh, yeah.
Thank you very much
That designated driver
He must be an accomplice
When I woke up from a drugged sleep,
I made them move a box of apples.
‘These are apples from the orchard.
'Take some'
Huh? Hey, hey, hey
- It's heavy~ Oh...
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
and i
I got back in the car and fell asleep.
I guess they replaced it with a money box.
Because the box weight will be different
Oh, isn't this fun?
You did a lot of research
What is research?
Fraudsters are so creative
There it is
You worked hard on the novel, but
But you know?
anyway…
ah…
Nothing anyway
You won't be able to prove it.
Genes are so scary.
That family P.N.
Well, I guess something like that flows.
Shameless
Jeokbanjajang, something like that
You know because they investigated my background, right?
my mother case
As I judge your father
Do you know what surprised me the most?
You don't remember me at all
The children of workers who had their hands cut off
I wasn't interested
You guys are that kind of people.
In the eyes of others
It makes me cry tears of blood
They say you don’t know me…
You know what surprised me the most?
my father before my eyes
Even after being brutally detained by the court
You don't remember me at all
The defendant is detained in court
- Okay, Judge! No
- Execute
Everyone please stand up
Father!
Wait a minute, father...
- ah…
- Judge! hey…
Ah, father! Oh, wait a minute.
Hey, judge!
Judge!
What do you think, a better human being?
huh?
How will you take responsibility?
Chairman Jang Hyun-bae was found not guilty.
The business world was turned upside down.
business rankings
Business owners ranked in the top 5
Arrested in court without evidence?
David Kang, this man
Are you sane?
I
I'll take care of it
somehow
What?
How are you going to fix it?
Such a person
I brought you to this place and sat you down
This is Attorney Oh.
which client
Would you trust us and entrust your case to us?
The Supreme Court found him not guilty, but
There is still a feeling of farewell and farewell...
Let's step down
Huh?
oh lawyer
Attorney Kim
This company was founded by my father.
Are you going to make me close here?
This is the will of the entire management team.
In the representative position
Please step aside
Attorney Oh Jeong-in
After…
under…
Hey, Reporter Kim, what's going on?
Chairman Jang Hyun-bae incident today
Did you know that it was overturned by the Supreme Court?
What does that mean?
Chairman Jang’s lawyers…
The defense team
I'm currently holding a press conference...
‘Former judge David Kang, who was in charge of the first trial’
‘After deciding on a conclusion’…
It's all about attacking Judge Kang.
Well, would you like to leave a comment?
Well, the Supreme Court Justice presiding over that decision...
Justice Shin Jung-seok
When Judge Kang was there, the Chief Judge of the Central District Court
Please leave a comment
Just hang up
As expected
Bar…
- Doctor
- Oh, hello!
sit, sit, sit
I'm doing things
Uh…
hello
I am a lawyer named Park Gi-ppeum.
This is Yoo Nan-hee
Ah, well…
Now, this is Jang Yeong-sil.
Hello, Doctor!
Always doing my best
Young lawyer Hwang Jun-woo!
It is said
yes
What's going on?
To this shabby place
Shabby?
When I do all this for you
These are the trial materials I've been digging into all night.
- Ah...
- Here
It's like my hometown
- Ah...
- Please sit down, doctor.
yes, yes
- No, no, that's enough, that's enough.
- Yes
our public interest team
In the meantime
The performance was great, yes.
I was so indifferent
I called you already
Even if it's encouragement
I should have done it once
No, doctor.
Our team worked on this firm
Just for letting me stay
thank you
I just said that
It looks a bit bony, doesn't it?
No, Dr. Park.
That, that…
Park, that's not what Attorney Park said...
Attorney Park
Request to sue lawyer David Kang
I heard a case came in?
Yes, doctor.
Why don't you take that case?
- Yes?
- Doctor
How can we...
You guys are public interest lawyers?
When a victim of a powerful crime comes to visit
Isn’t it your job to help?
Oh, was I wrong?
Doctor
That's true, but
This is our team leader.
Rather than taking it upon ourselves
Connecting other public events...
my instructions
If you have a friend you don't want to follow
Talk, now.
Let's see if it's there
Well then, thank you for your hard work
Doctor
We are public interest lawyers
In order to determine public interest, at least
After hearing Attorney Kang’s position,
I think it's right to decide
Listening to both sides
Isn’t this the basics of being a lawyer, doctor?
Kang David
Did you learn it from that friend?
in front of me
Basic thing to look for
Yes?
yes
Let’s start with the basics.
Like public defenders
Come in!
under…
what's the matter?
Yes~
Ai, Judge Kang
It's been a while
sit down, that way
Hello after a long time
Supreme Court Justice
this way
sit down
Ah…
Uh, uh
Pu’er tea, this is
Have you grown a lot of gray hair?
Don't even talk
Supreme Court Justice This position
The day of inauguration and the day of retirement
Just two days
It's a nice place
Very busy with work
Are you saying you're about to get crushed to death?
I thought you wouldn't accept the interview.
I just came empty handed.
Huh?
I am Judge Kang
Is there any reason not to meet you?
Ah~
Maybe
Chairman Jang Hyun-bae incident?
Oh my, that's it
Each person decides based on their convictions.
Ah, yes
No way Judge Kang
Because of that
You didn’t come here because you were sad, right?
Hey, hey, can it be like that?
Even if not
Just thinking about you
I feel bad
Still go outside
It seems like you are more active?
We do a lot of interesting things
Oh, is that so?
Jaebeom Yoo just met me.
What?
Why did you do that?
uh…
Well, what do you mean?
After meeting that person
I'm sure you understand
that video
Who did you trust and make it?
What are you talking about now?
Director
I really liked that director.
You trusted me without any doubts.
He even put me in charge of the corruption department.
It's me
If it weren't for the director...
In such a clumsy video
It wouldn't have gotten this far
A person I always trusted and followed
found a money box
The person who would have reported it first
Is that true?
Yes, Chief Justice.
No, no one gave it to me.
Such a large amount of money
Was it in the judge's car?
Who believes that?
before it becomes known
Should I cover it up as I quietly take off my clothes?
Or to a habitual fraudster
on suspicion of receiving a large sum of money
Will I be investigated by the police?
I'll cover it for you
If you tell me to quietly resign and leave,
A person who had no choice but to follow
Because that person is an accomplice
It was possible.
What kind of nonsense are you saying now?
Are you making a fuss?
haha…
Jaebeom Yoo embroidered it
Well, you are a loser.
Supreme Court Justice of a country
An accomplice to a habitual fraudster
Hey, as long as Yoo Jae-beom opens his mouth
Korea is going to be in chaos.
I couldn't protect you
I understand you're disappointed, but
Oh my
My mental illness was very deep.
It would be a good idea to get some counseling.
It's a pity
A friend who had a gun like that...
Oh my
Judge
I just met Shin Jung-seok and dreamed of it.
Jaebeom Yoo surrendered
Shin Jung-seok didn’t know
Is that really true?
I pretend not to
He was embarrassed
It's definitely true
Baby, then
Did Jaebeom Yoo turn himself in arbitrarily?
I don't know, that's
Or
Is there another mastermind?
Well, anyway
Because I came out to scare you a lot.
I'm sure something will move
Ah, yes
Are you telling me to catch up?
But
Now with hazard pay
Are you giving it to me, Judge?
- This again...
- Good luck!
Ha…
Uh, Jeongin.
Now?
You resigned from your position as CEO?
why?
Ha, it's because of me
Ha…
no
It was my decision anyway
I called my brother
That's me
I'll try to fix it somehow
- First of all...
- Think about tomorrow's work tomorrow
Let's have a drink today
Now
Ha…
brother
uh
You were hurt a lot back then, right?
During the training center
What, I kicked it?
Ah, why isn’t it like you?
Are you talking about old times?
I'm sorry
my dad
Surprisingly, she was a total idiot.
I dare
She was a daughter who could not disobey her father.
Even if it's like me, I'll separate you
With O&Partners Princess
A high school graduate
I understand
Enough
But remember?
The day we broke up
A promise we made while drinking
Well…
You forgot?
I did that back then
‘Later, until I was forty years old.
'If we don't meet each other'
‘Let’s meet again then and get married.’
I turned 40 today
Ah…
It's an awesome birthday, right?
I'll buy the alcohol today
It's birthday chin
Ha…
why…
‘Debt collection notice’?
What does this mean?
'JC Capital'
What's going on, on the way to work?
You're not even in the office.
It's uncomfortable anyway.
Well, everyone was avoiding me.
Because everyone is suffering
Ha…
Because everyone likes Attorney Kang.
While I like it
Why such a scammer?
Does everyone have fun?
A rigged trial?
Why do I do that?
What is there to gain?
You became a star because of that incident, right?
Did you do a lot of media interviews?
Hey, I'm trying to float
They even had a rigged trial?
still me
I see you as a career-crazy piece of trash.
great
What about our public interest lawyers?
What is it?
Jaebeom Yoo
This is a text message sent with a video.
We never talked about texting!
Because I trusted Attorney Kang!
yes?
During Byul’s case and Kang Hoon’s case,
I got to see Attorney Kang again.
Although he pretends to be indifferent on the outside,
You were always sincere, Attorney Kang.
'This kind of person
'I couldn't have done something like that.'
I believed it from the beginning
So this nonsense
I ignored the text.
the apple box
That video is the only one I
Do you know how many times I've seen it again?
'It's definitely some kind of manipulation.'
I did that
To find out...
Park Byeon
Are you really going to take my case?
Everyone says they will do it?
Everyone hates doing it!
Still, I can't help it.
Moreover, Dr. Kyu-Jang Oh
I instructed it directly.
Take charge of the case
Are you Dr. Oh Gyu-jang?
So
Please tell me everything
Everyone listen to Attorney Kang’s story.
I decided to make a decision
Yes?
Ah, in such a hurry...
Hey, Hwang Junwoo
Uh, over there…
Why...
Oh, Joy Sister
Uh, I'll tell everyone to gather around.
This is bittersweet
With a case in which I am a party
This is how we hold meetings
I don't want to believe it
Lawyer Kang
You said there was a rigged trial...
Then you just have to not believe it, right?
Boy, everyone says such scammers
Do you believe it, everyone?
In the meantime, we
I did some research.
What investigation?
Ah, I had a job from 10 years ago.
What do you mean you investigated?
This is...
yes
When that incident
that moved public opinion
It's a photo.
Lawyer Kang
He handed it to the reporter.
What does that mean?
We
I reviewed all of the trial records at that time.
nowhere
There was no picture of this
The student who died
There is also a statement that he brought cup ramen.
It's nowhere.
alternative
This photo…
What picture is this? Lawyer Kang
This is the issue in that case
What does it matter?
We too
I don't want to think like this
Lawyer Kang
But
In this case, Attorney Kang
first received national attention
It was an incident
Since then, he has held key positions one after another.
You've been victorious
Ha…
Lawyer Kang
Please tell me now
I can't help it
Everyone treats me like that
They see me as a person who is crazy about success.
Ah, Attorney Kang.
Anyway, through Yoo Jae-beom
Because you will know everything
I will speak first with my own mouth
Yoo Baek-man
That human and me
There is a deep relationship
Yes?
ah…
Mom, I'm here!
mom
Mom?
- Ah...
- Mom, Mom
uh
Ah, David is here.
I'm sorry
You're coming, but I can't even meet you...
That's not important, now
- Oh, I have a fever, why are you telling me...
- Ugh!
Ah, ah, it's okay
Oh, it's okay
I'm fine
It's no big deal
Uh…
Mom, why are your hands like this?
Mom's hand...
mom
mom hand
Speak up!
mom
Anyway
Take care of your mind, everyone.
- Let go! Let go!
- Don't be weak-hearted.
What is this?
- What, what, you bastard!
- Come to work!
you
Suddenly, an additional order came in.
How many days have you been making your mom work overtime?
not even a few pennies
Because of that damn money! Mr.
Ouch! Mr.
Hey, quickly, quickly, quickly!
Where did you get that bastard! Mr.
- Let go! Mr.
-Are you okay?
Let go!
Take that away!
Student, hurry up!
uh? Hey, hey
- Hey!
- Let go!
Go, go!
Stop it, oh
- Student!
- Come out and see me.
The little bastard is spoiled, Mr.
What kind of thug action is this, what kind of thug action is this?
Hey
Don't act like this here ignorantly.
Go and do it by the law, by the law!
I guess he's a big guy without a father.
Mr…
In our situation
What kind of lawsuit are you filing?
Where do you get the money for a lawyer?
I'll do it
Because I will do everything
I hope mom gets better quickly
Oh, you still
They say it’s because they don’t know the world.
Who can help a house like ours?
There's no one, David.
So
You go to college...
I do it, mom
yes
Oh my
Did the support manager come out?
Oh my, when did you retire?
It's a support letter.
Sorry for being late, your honor.
Oh no, no
Let's argue.
Ha…
But
I'm sorry about this, so what should I do?
The information requested by the plaintiff is
Because there are so many
some time to prepare
If you give generously
Thank you
Your honor
This is already my third change request.
Lower your voice
This is a sacred court
David…
Please sit down
Today's hearing date has been changed.
The next date is
I will specify it later
everyone in their seats
Please stand up
Your honor!
david
David
Huh?
Those with money and power
how to protect yourself
I knew it so well
So the trial
It took a year and a half
Giving up on college
I tried hanging on
What is the result...
submitted by the plaintiff
Evidence alone
To prove the defendant's negligence
Because it's not enough
The claim for damages in this case is
I reject this for no reason.
Your honor
everyone in their seats
Please stand up
Your honor
There's proof here, proof!
- Your honor, your honor!
- David...
ah…
mom
- Ah...
- Mom
Mom, are you okay? mom
Mom!
Just two things
promise me
I must
Make me cremated and sprinkle it in the river.
Every year for no reason
Mom said she was coming to visit me
Don't do that
Okay?
mom
Don't look back
Only forward
keep going
David, you must
I need to get ahead in life
I have to succeed
Live without being ignored
As far as I can go
Be sure to go
my son
Okay?
mom
Mom, no, mom
no, mom
my mom
died like that
The boss
Only then
Throwing away a few pennies in consolation money
It was everything
mom
Even though I
The promise to sprinkle water in the river
I couldn't keep it
As far as you can go
promise to go
I will definitely protect that
I'll definitely let you go, mom.
Lawyer Kang…
That's why I became a lawyer
I'm no different from you
like my mom
So that no one is unfair
Fair to everyone
applying the law
I wanted to be that kind of judge.
I am
Doing something embarrassing to my mom
I'm a person who can't do it
As a human being, I have many shortcomings.
As a judge
I never crossed that line
I'm sorry
I am
I didn't even know you had experienced something like that.
I behaved very badly
Ah, I just walked the road to success.
I just thought they were unlucky elites...
I understand
I kinda
There's a lot of cuteness
Especially
I guess it's true that I'm unlucky
Lawyer Kang
Ha, I had no idea either.
It was very difficult, right?
At that young age...
no
What
I'm the only one who went through difficult times
That's not true
What do you think?
at least
You didn't decide to avoid it?
huh?
In the past with defendant Yoo Man-man
If something bad like that happened
Shouldn’t you have avoided it?
For a fair trial?
- Hwang Jun-woo...
- uh?
am i wrong?
Junwoo is right.
Attorney Park
Attorney Kang, do you remember?
My name is Yoo Baek-man.
When I first took it out
You know me as Yoo Baek-man, right?
Who is that?
I don't know that person
You said you didn’t know, right?
A name you can't help but know...
Oh my, that's it
Because I suddenly heard it
I was momentarily mistaken...
I'm talking about a rigged trial.
Because I suddenly brought it out
How did you react?
Jaebeom Yoo
Lawyer Kang
I believe it was a rigged trial.
Sounds that don't even sound like words...
Hey, I
Do you look like that kind of person?
A rigged trial? What are you looking at me for?
You taught me
Human instinctive defense response
If nothing like that happens
Without any unnecessary sacrifices
He probably denied it right away.
'I'm not a bad person'
‘How do you view me’, blah blah blah
like this
It's a needless thing to do
It is an instinctive human defense response.
That's right
In the end, the long story I just told you...
under…
You taught me
To those of us who knew nothing
Of course it's Soyeon's fault.
Uh, let's talk about it in detail.
That's just the motive for the crime.
Attorney Park
Lawyer Kang spoke with great difficulty.
That painful story
In the end, very powerful
It's the motive for the crime.
Isn't it?
Did you learn well from me?
yes?
yes
i did that
Lawyer Kang!
Oh, I really did it.
Rigged trial?
Ha, really?
Because we're not on the same side anymore
I should also exercise my right to remain silent.
See you in court, everyone.
Ha…
under…
Don't you have a lawyer?
I am my own lawyer.
These are people who have nothing to do with me.
- Because the level is not right.
- Ha!
ha ha ha!
- Now, father-in-law...
- Now, craftsman…
If you didn't do Undercover
What should I do?
Did you learn well?
As of today
Public Interest Litigation Team Approval Line
You know that because you changed it to me.
If you put yourself under someone like that
Pro Bono Team
You won't be able to do anything
If the team can't do anything
I guess I'll have to lay off
The lawyer follows the instructions of his/her law firm.
Is working weird?
I will hire a lawyer.
David Kang, defendant's lawyer
This is Oh Jeong-in
What is the human heart?
Is it that simple?
Others carelessly
Can I cut it?
‘For something I have no authority to do.
In case of intervention'
‘It does not constitute a crime’
'not guilty'
The defendant's sincerity
I'd like to hear it
My desire for revenge on Mr. Yoo Baek-man
at the defendant's trial
Did it have an impact?